[{"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbaa", "question": "What citrus \u00adflavored soft drink was introduced by Coca-Cola in 1979 to compete with Pepsi's Mountain Dew?", "answer": "Mello Yello", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fede5b66ce05a3942286def", "question": "Which American television sitcom is about a witch who marries an ordinary man and lives as a suburban housewife?", "answer": "\"Bewitched\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133953e", "question": "What show starring Robert Ulrich was a spin-off from \"The Rookies\"?", "answer": "S.W.A.T.", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff0ae8de662d71a53650fba", "question": "Shostakovich's Symphony No. 7 is a musical tribute to which battle of World War II?", "answer": "The 900-Day Siege of Leningrad", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe6ab5020565ad31a57c828", "question": "Who said, \"Pleasure is the bait of sin\"?", "answer": "Plato", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fecc3d8ec223966ae8f8881", "question": "Where does Brooks in the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\" work after he got out of prison?", "answer": "A grocery store", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea3985ff048f679a45ab28", "question": "What is the smallest organ in the human body?", "answer": "Pineal gland", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fef5f6c6ce05a3942286e42", "question": "Where is Paddington Bear from?", "answer": "Peru", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe3ecf58b5801b8f54a7faf", "question": "Peleus and Thetis were the parents of what famed warrior?", "answer": "Achilles", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a523", "question": "What is the capital of Lithuania?", "answer": "Vilnius", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391af", "question": "Who dramatically kissed Halle Berry on stage when he won Best Actor?", "answer": "Adrien Brody", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58f16690f7c52aae91cc07af", "question": "What is New Year's Eve called in Scotland?", "answer": "Hogmanay", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338eb2", "question": "What Broadway musical featured the song \"New York, New York\"?", "answer": "On the Town", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bcc", "question": "What did God create on the fourth day?", "answer": "The Sun, the Moon and the Stars", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5a9e92d97ccba3ffe45786bd", "question": "Who wrote the 1932 comic novel \"Cold Comfort Farm\"?", "answer": "Stella Gibbons", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ae862267f28483af1e7fdc6", "question": "Who was the author of the novel \"War and Peace\"?", "answer": "Leo Tolstoy", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5c77d25d24f0f7a362efd552", "question": "Which civilizations created the basis for modern day peanut butter?", "answer": "The Ancient Incas and Aztecs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b052", "question": "Former Yugoslavian leader Josip Broz was also known by what other name?", "answer": "Tito", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59e6b2fffb6c85e9e634ff41", "question": "Despite being released at the end of 1998, who had a  #1 hit in 1999 with the song \"Fly Away\"?", "answer": "Lenny Kravitz", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f68", "question": "What volcano did the early Romans believe was the forge of Vulcan, the God of Fire?", "answer": "Mount Etna", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a42c", "question": "The Himalayas are located on which continent?", "answer": "Asia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393da", "question": "The movie \"Heart Like a Wheel\" was a story about which drag racing legend?", "answer": "Shirley Muldowney", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7ea", "question": "Which US state is named after a King of England?", "answer": "Georgia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f91", "question": "What is Goldfinger's first name?", "answer": "Auric", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ce3", "question": "What film's title character is the only one who can see a giant demonic rabbit name Frank?", "answer": "Donnie Darko", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9d5", "question": "What does a manometer measure?", "answer": "Pressure", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c625", "question": "How many stars does Aries consist of?", "answer": "4", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339953", "question": "What is the name of the skunk in \"Bambi\"?", "answer": "Flower", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af13", "question": "What city hosted the Winter Olympics in 1932?", "answer": "Lake Placid", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c71d", "question": "What is a tanager?", "answer": "A bird", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be1b", "question": "What gets changed by the process of transubstantiation?", "answer": "The Catholic Eucharist wafer and wine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133914e", "question": "Who was the Greek god of craftsmen?", "answer": "Hephaestus", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7cefa877e98cb97778a48", "question": "What is the lowest natural point on Earth?", "answer": "The Challenger Deep", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3e6", "question": "What was the first NASA program to land an object on Mars that sent information back to Earth?", "answer": "Viking", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd968cd23c87fd04dd15e04", "question": "How long did it take Sir Francis Drake to sail around the world in 1580?", "answer": "3 years", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c056", "question": "Which bird is the national bird of Israel?", "answer": "Hoopoe", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bb1", "question": "What are the seven deadly sins?", "answer": "Greed, Envy, Gluttony, Sloth, Lust, Pride And Wrath", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59e80464de59ea584496fea4", "question": "What are the names of the two adult Dalmatians in the novel \"The Hundred and One Dalmatians\"?", "answer": "Pongo and Missis", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5e8", "question": "Mallard and Ruddy are species of what bird?", "answer": "Duck", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ffa42b5c73aa70ea0b70b14", "question": "Fort-de-France is the capital of what country?", "answer": "Martinique", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133925a", "question": "Which town's businesses include the \"I Can't Believe It's a Law Firm\" and \"J.R.R. Toykins\"?", "answer": "Springfield's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a374", "question": "What is the capital of Romania?", "answer": "Bucharest", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338929", "question": "Which Wagner opera shares its name with a doomed ship?", "answer": "The Flying Dutchman", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133caf3", "question": "What medical term is used to describe the process of sweating?", "answer": "Hydrosis", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fdffcb41cf6db9ac4808d02", "question": "Which U.S. city is known as \"The Emerald City\"?", "answer": "Seattle", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a70f", "question": "Which is the largest Great Lake?", "answer": "Lake Superior", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5cb70d0ef96e155acab35d31", "question": "In what year were the first Academy Awards ceremony held?", "answer": "1929", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca97", "question": "What animal may be Stag, Rhinoceros or Dung?", "answer": "Beetle", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5a4a996e61d1b4d384d5d69a", "question": "What TV network was home to the TV show \"Gunsmoke\"?", "answer": "CBS", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7a0", "question": "According to the Gospels, what did the Wise Men bring?", "answer": "Gold, Frankincense, and Myrrh", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fec8bb1ec223966ae8f8841", "question": "What year was the first Super Bowl played?", "answer": "1967", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af44", "question": "What war ended at the Battle of San Jacinto?", "answer": "Texas Revolution", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7c21d877e98cb97778986", "question": "Which U.S. state is known as the Flickertail State?", "answer": "North Dakota", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8f1", "question": "A Phon is a unit of what?", "answer": "Loudness", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd668bba5bfecdd737e0872", "question": "Which religion has the most gods?", "answer": "Hinduism", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b88", "question": "What Looney Toons cartoon character often used the catchphrase \"Thufferin' Thuccotash\"?", "answer": "Sylvester the cat", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133935c", "question": "In what city did the TV show \"Full House\" take place?", "answer": "San Francisco", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b17448fbb2d29f81593b6fb", "question": "Nat King Cole died in which year?", "answer": "1965", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338aed", "question": "What is Charlie's last name in Roald Dahl's \"Charlie and the Chocolate Factory\"?", "answer": "Bucket", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c259", "question": "What is another name for tetanus?", "answer": "Lockjaw", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397ae", "question": "What did Leonard Nimoy need a new pair of every few days in the late 1960's?", "answer": "Ears", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391d4", "question": "What is E.T.'s job in the Spielberg movie?", "answer": "Botanist", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecca54ec223966ae8f8899", "question": "In the film \"The Shawshank Redemption,\" what was Andrew Dufresne's profession?", "answer": "Andy was a banker", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febab387e83c707845b20e6", "question": "What is the only dwarf planet in the asteroid belt between Mars and Jupiter?", "answer": "Ceres", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ab99c6121a8909e5c332d35", "question": "Which band released the album \"Breakfast in America\"?", "answer": "Supertramp", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d37", "question": "What popular comic book character was created by Jerry Siegel and Joe Shuster?", "answer": "Superman", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339208", "question": "What pop star posed naked and pregnant on the August 2006 cover of Harper's Bazaar?", "answer": "Britney Spears", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b738", "question": "Tennis player Margaret Smith Court who holds a record 62 Grand Slam titles is from which country?", "answer": "Australia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c18", "question": "According to Exodus, what is the second plague of Egypt?", "answer": "Frogs", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b066", "question": "In 1967, what company introduced the first consumer model of microwave oven designed for home use?", "answer": "Amana", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59a552833e1c6f9840ba3197", "question": "The telephone country code 82 would connect you with which country?", "answer": "South Korea", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c657", "question": "How many horns does the average African black rhino have?", "answer": "Two", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff213af31a458464a93c451", "question": "Pineapples, kiwis and papayas contain enzymes that can do what to meat?", "answer": "Tenderize it", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59ded085ea2747c8aff16d29", "question": "Ireland's River Shannon drains which basin?", "answer": "Shannon River Basin", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fea78c8ff048f679a45abdd", "question": "Gray, blue, bowhead and finback are varieties of what?", "answer": "Whales", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59008ff3cf842fa4c4ba96c2", "question": "Who created the fictional character Tristram Shandy?", "answer": "Laurence Sterne", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "600cc10a6de0eb824d4052dc", "question": "Which continent has no active volcanoes?", "answer": "Australia -- All of its volcanoes are dormant, including Tweed Volcano, one of the largest extinct volcanoes in the world.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5eb738325e259d786908732e", "question": "What book by George Orwell had a film adaption that was funded by the CIA?", "answer": "Animal Farm", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ca4", "question": "Who wrote the 1903 novel \"Call of the Wild\"?", "answer": "Jack London", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59675bac2b59efe0e9417e90", "question": "Whose \"Hicktown\" country music singer first hit single debuted on the radio in 2005?", "answer": "Jason Aldean", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e26", "question": "What did Benjamin Britten write the \"Young Person's Guide to\" in 1945?", "answer": "The Orchestra", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5c77ccce24f0f7a362efd53f", "question": "What strait separates New Zealand's North and South Islands?", "answer": "Cook Strait", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb87", "question": "What TV evangelist was sent to prison for defrauding followers of his PTL Ministry out of $158 million?", "answer": "Jim Bakker", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe73894eec85e375820b264", "question": "What is the driest continent?", "answer": "Antarctica", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5febb9a07e83c707845b213c", "question": "What common sensation has the scientific name \"sphenopalatine ganglioneuralgia\"?", "answer": "Brain freeze", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b724", "question": "Danish postmaster Einar Holboll is credited with the 1903 creation of what?", "answer": "Christmas Seals", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf76", "question": "What is the fear of getting wrinkles known as?", "answer": "Rhytiphobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "591c382d815febcc896f927b", "question": "What is the eleventh sign of the Zodiac?", "answer": "Aquarius", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59068002ff9c0647b50a8089", "question": "What motoring show premiered on Amazon Video on November 18, 2016?", "answer": "The Grand Tour", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58dba256874c93a3298b2131", "question": "In Greek mythology, who did Zeus place in the heavens as the constellation Ursa Major?", "answer": "Callisto", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f70", "question": "In Greek mythology, where were lotuses eaten?", "answer": "Island of Jerba", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391b0", "question": "Who played the role of Andy Dufresne in the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\"?", "answer": "Tim Robbins", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6008dcacf4f3bc4a292f861b", "question": "How many times was Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. arrested?", "answer": "29 (Many of the charges against him were illegitimate and the result of widespread, systemic racism.)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdc3", "question": "According to the KFC ads, how many herbs and spices are in Colonel's secret recipe?", "answer": "Eleven", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fefbfda6ce05a3942286f06", "question": "Who recorded the song \"Tango in the Night\"?", "answer": "Fleetwood Mac", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5cefc060948005ec986edcda", "question": "Who is the first member of the group LOONA to debut?", "answer": "Heejin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "590681c6ff9c0647b50a8097", "question": "Under what name did Nintendo re-release the Nintendo Entertainment System in 2016?", "answer": "Nintendo Entertainment System: NES Classic Edition", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf8f", "question": "The \"Intelligent Whale\" was the nickname of an early what?", "answer": "Submarine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af01", "question": "What queen was the last ruler of Hawaii before it joined the US?", "answer": "Queen Liliuokalani", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe8f15101dd7bf43be5e804", "question": "What is the name of the gigantic silver sphere at EPCOT?", "answer": "Spaceship Earth", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a41e", "question": "What is the modern day equivalent of Formosa?", "answer": "Taiwan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5a25f1596682715b82711cdf", "question": "What year was the ice cream cone patented in UK?", "answer": "1902", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5971e0fd89261e916c8e09b0", "question": "Which European city is the game \"Assassin's Creed Unity\" set in?", "answer": "Paris", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8f4", "question": "What do you have if you are suffering from circadian dysrhythmia?", "answer": "Jet lag", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab40", "question": "What place is also known as \"land nearest nowhere\"?", "answer": "Cape Three Points", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339560", "question": "In the movie It's a Wonderful Life, who lost $8,000?", "answer": "Uncle Billy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7f6", "question": "What Italian scientist discovered methane and invented the first battery?", "answer": "Alessandro Volta", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ad7e759b24f84e0b9f9ffb8", "question": "Which Star Wars villain shares a voice with the narrator of the 1995 film \"Judge Dredd\"?", "answer": "Darth Vader", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59a5525f3e1c6f9840ba3194", "question": "Where was the Armistice, between the Allies and Germany, signed on November 11, 1918?", "answer": "Compiegne", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c6f1", "question": "What is the longest nerve in the human body?", "answer": "Sciatic nerve", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fea380fff048f679a45ab20", "question": "What is the scientific name for the job or role an organism plays in its habitat?", "answer": "Niche", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc1b", "question": "What team bought Babe Ruth from the Boston Red Sox?", "answer": "The New York Yankees", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe7ccff877e98cb97778a30", "question": "What shape is in the center of Switzerland's flag?", "answer": "Cross", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c887", "question": "Chemically, what kind of acid is stomach acid?", "answer": "Hydrochloric acid", "category": "science"}, {"id": "601b4bba49076251badbeac7", "question": "How many rooms are there in Buckingham Palace (total number)?", "answer": "775 -- It includes 19 State rooms, 92 offices, 52 Royal and guest bedrooms, 188 bedrooms for staff and 78 bathrooms.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5f178122b8195c09b948d5c1", "question": "Who was the emperor of Ethiopia from 1930 to 1974?", "answer": "Haile Selassie", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392d4", "question": "Mickey Mouse's faithful dog Pluto was originally known by what name?", "answer": "Rover", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aeb1", "question": "Over what part of Captain Robert Jenkins were Britain and Spain at war in 1739?", "answer": "His ear", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afaa", "question": "St. Albans was the start and Bosworth field was the finish of what?", "answer": "War of the Roses", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a092", "question": "Who sang \"That's Alright Mama\"?", "answer": "Elvis Presley", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a736", "question": "The city of Cleveland is located on the shores of which Great Lake?", "answer": "Lake Erie", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd2d22a2596a59cbdfbd38b", "question": "Where is \"The Lush Valley of the Mills\"?", "answer": "Italy", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d4f", "question": "What actress shaved her head for her role in the movie \"THX 1138\"?", "answer": "Maggie McOmie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d58", "question": "What's the name of Mario's girlfriend, kidnapped by the giant ape in \"Donkey Kong\"?", "answer": "Pauline", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8aaae01dd7bf43be5e75e", "question": "If someone said \"you are olid\", what would they mean?", "answer": "You smell extremely unpleasant", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59f9b99a364247bf200fb88e", "question": "Ostraconophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Shellfish", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391ac", "question": "What is Homer Simpson's middle initial?", "answer": "J", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8e4", "question": "St. Louis' Gateway Arch is officially named for what US president?", "answer": "Thomas Jefferson", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5b3231cebf195a31e15d7387", "question": "Also known as the \"Chile Pine\", what is the common name of the tree \"Araucaria araucana\"?", "answer": "Monkey puzzle", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5a9e97197ccba3ffe45786f8", "question": "Melissophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Bees", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ee1", "question": "What bird was used as an alias for Tom Clancy's CIA agent in the Kremlin?", "answer": "The Cardinal", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c483", "question": "In what decade was the very first test-tube baby born?", "answer": "1970s", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5febaa667e83c707845b20df", "question": "Which colors are at the extreme ends of the visible color spectrum?", "answer": "Red and violet", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7b4", "question": "What was studied by Project Blue Book?", "answer": "UFOs", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4d9", "question": "How many US states are named after a president?", "answer": "One - Washington", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab7c", "question": "Freetown is the capital of which African country?", "answer": "Sierra Leone", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5b5", "question": "What relative of the raccoon is sometimes known as the cat-bear?", "answer": "The Panda", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b71f", "question": "What country had, at one time, a female \"Santa\" called La Befena?", "answer": "Italy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adf3", "question": "In what city did the Hindenburg airship disaster occur?", "answer": "Lakehurst, New Jersey", "category": "history"}, {"id": "597cdcc1e347d002c297e4eb", "question": "President Richard Nixon called what songstress an \"Ambassador of Love\"?", "answer": "Pearl Baily", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6aac020565ad31a57c820", "question": "During the American Revolution, who was known as the Swamp Fox?", "answer": "Lt. Col. Francis Marion", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b668", "question": "What is the length-to-width ratio of a regulation pool table?", "answer": "2:1", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd96b5423c87fd04dd15e1a", "question": "1816 was known as the year without what?", "answer": "Summer", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4e1", "question": "What do you get when you mix scotch, sweet vermouth and angostura bitters?", "answer": "A Rob Roy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb2c", "question": "In what country is Absolut vodka made?", "answer": "Sweden", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5909cfb6bb53d1af658864f5", "question": "The song \"Jingle Bell Rock\" is performed during the opening credits of which \"Lethal Weapon\" film?", "answer": "The first one", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58dba71e874c93a3298b2161", "question": "What is Ace Frehley\u2019s persona name in the band KISS?", "answer": "Spaceman or Space Ace", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5f0", "question": "How many white stripes are there on the American flag?", "answer": "Six", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffa416fc73aa70ea0b70b0f", "question": "Which Hawaiian island is entirely privately owned?", "answer": "Ni'ihau (The island was purched by wealthy Scottish plantation owners from King Kamehameha V in 1864 for $10,000 in gold.)", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff20e6e31a458464a93c422", "question": "In which Franz Kafka novel did the main character turn into a cockroach?", "answer": "Metamorphosis", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf69", "question": "How many segments are there for the number 8 on a digital clock?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aebd", "question": "Which part of his anatomy did Lord Nelson lose first?", "answer": "One of his eyes", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5921fdfea4edfd43a087adcc", "question": "Disney's 2013 film \"Frozen\" was inspired by which fairy tale?", "answer": "The Snow Queen", "category": "art"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c93d", "question": "What bird is the smallest living bird?", "answer": "Bee Hummingbird", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3bf", "question": "In 1917 Lucy Slowe was the first US what?", "answer": "African-American tennis champion", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a447", "question": "Which river runs through Paris?", "answer": "Seine", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133966a", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", which character has a pacemaker?", "answer": "Krusty", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399e4", "question": "What actor played Ross and Monica\u2019s father, Jack, on the TV show \"Friends\"?", "answer": "Elliot Gould", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a8d", "question": "In the series \"Eragon\", what is the name of Eragon's dragon?", "answer": "Saphira", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a672", "question": "The city of Albuquerque is located in what desert?", "answer": "Chihuahua Desert", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b789", "question": "What underdog knocked out Mike Tyson in Tokyo in 1990?", "answer": "Buster Douglas", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59decf2fea2747c8aff16d1b", "question": "What is sometimes referred to as Zulu time?", "answer": "Greenwich Mean Time", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5febb6947e83c707845b2129", "question": "What is the name for the boundary around a black hole?", "answer": "Event Horizon", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b220", "question": "What city was Billy Clanton killed in?", "answer": "Tombstone", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1be", "question": "What US president was a personal friend of Nathaniel Hawthorne?", "answer": "Franklin Pierce", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa81", "question": "In which US state is Mount Vernon?", "answer": "Virginia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f84", "question": "The Michael Douglas film \"A Perfect Murder\" is a remake of what 1950s thriller?", "answer": "Dial M for Murder", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015ff43fe83fe1f2a824c4c", "question": "Why did US President Theodore Roosevelt ban Christmas trees in the White House in 1901?", "answer": "He banned the trees during his first year in office due to him being \"a devoted environmentalist\".", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe3ea2d38e4e5d4832e6313", "question": "What airline owned the 747 blown up by a terrorist bomb over Lockerbie, Scotland in 1988?", "answer": "PanAm", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5a7", "question": "In which state was the first Wal-Mart store opened?", "answer": "Arkansas", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133937d", "question": "In the movie \"Interview with the Vampire\", who cut Lestat's throat?", "answer": "Claudia", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338dd6", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"guitar\"?", "answer": "Spanish", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133949e", "question": "Who wrote the novel the miniseries \"Shogun\" was based on?", "answer": "James Clavell", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe6a88120565ad31a57c7f6", "question": "Which American author was awarded both the Nobel Prize in Literature and Presidential Medal of Freedom?", "answer": "John Steinbeck", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5e147a756ca6dac04a20ca4f", "question": "When did Thomas Jefferson purchase the territory of Louisiana?", "answer": "1803", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339408", "question": "Who directed the 2003 movie \"Monster\"?", "answer": "Patty Jenkins", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b92d", "question": "What game has the winner striking the loser's wrist with two extended fingers?", "answer": "Rock, Paper, Scissors", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393fd", "question": "Who co-wrote, directed and starred in the 1971 movie \"Bananas\"?", "answer": "Woody Allen", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2d5", "question": "What military legend was nicknamed \"Old Fuss and Feathers\"?", "answer": "Winfield Scott", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9fa", "question": "What does ZIP as in ZIP code stand for?", "answer": "Zone Improvement Project", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bae7", "question": "In what year did both \"Mad Magazine\" and \"The National Enquirer\" debut?", "answer": "1952", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea7ca1ff048f679a45abf8", "question": "What do you call a group of giraffes?", "answer": "A tower", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b29d", "question": "What US president loved Fresca so much he had a soda tap installed for the Oval Office?", "answer": "Lyndon Johnson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c7f", "question": "Who was the first African American woman to host a TV show?", "answer": "Oprah Winfrey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338cfe", "question": "On what date did the \"Dennis the Menace\" comic strip debut in newspapers?", "answer": "March 12, 1951", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fe1", "question": "Who is Lois Lane's younger sister?", "answer": "Lucy Lane", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399dd", "question": "Who was the original bandleader for \"The Tonight Show with Jay Leno\" from 1992 to 1995?", "answer": "Branford Marsalis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339378", "question": "Johann Van der Smut is better known as what?", "answer": "Goldmember", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339073", "question": "What is the author of \"The Bonesetter's Daughter\", \"The Joy Luck Club\", and \"Sagwa, the Chinese Siamese Cat\"?", "answer": "Amy Tan", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59636d9f967692ea851899af", "question": "The surface of what is typically 70% water and 10% ice?", "answer": "Earth", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe655a2ae7e414034b5aeb6", "question": "What was Henry Ford\u2019s original design for a car called?", "answer": "Quadricycle", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59e6ba50fb6c85e9e634ff50", "question": "Who composed \"Invitation to the Dance\" in 1819?", "answer": "Carl Maria von Weber", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7a0", "question": "What is the closest foreign country to the US which does not touch the US?", "answer": "Russia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9ec", "question": "The Kung San people live in what area of Africa?", "answer": "Kalahari Desert in Botswana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d3a", "question": "Who's responsible for \"The Ballad of Billy the Kid\"?", "answer": "Billy Joel", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c05b", "question": "Which bird is the national bird of Panama?", "answer": "Harpy eagle", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fdd5d0a0499cffc60b84230", "question": "Who led the Solidarity movement and became President of Poland in 1990?", "answer": "Lech Walesa", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339425", "question": "What is the name of Angelina Jolie's father?", "answer": "Jon Voight", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be33", "question": "How many players are there in a standard American football team?", "answer": "Eleven", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5ec", "question": "What everyday item did John Walker invent?", "answer": "Friction matches", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339be6", "question": "What year did the TV show \"Seinfeld\" debut in?", "answer": "1989", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea3572ff048f679a45ab02", "question": "What color is Mars\u2019 sunset?", "answer": "Blue", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5cefc100948005ec986edce2", "question": "Who is the ninth member of the group LOONA to debut?", "answer": "Yves", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b88a", "question": "In which decade was the first aluminum bat used in professional baseball?", "answer": "1970s", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae87", "question": "What did the US government purchase from Spain in 1819?", "answer": "Florida", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca3d", "question": "Which element appears ninth on the periodic table?", "answer": "Fluorine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b477", "question": "What year did Arthur W. Savage patent the radial tire?", "answer": "1915", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff25b8031a458464a93c478", "question": "In what year was the McDonald's Happy Meal created?", "answer": "Originally fielded in 1977 and ultimately released nationwide in 1979", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b38e", "question": "Which crew sank in the 1978 Boat Race?\u00a0", "answer": "Cambridge", "category": "history"}, {"id": "594d06e21a1c922dd1ac64b1", "question": "Pont Neuf is the oldest bridge over the river Seine, located in which French city?", "answer": "Paris", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be1c", "question": "What novelist's father, Bronson, was one of the founders of the Transcendentalist movement?", "answer": "Louisa May Alcott's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0f2", "question": "What WWII European recovery program was named for the Secretary of State who proposed it?", "answer": "Marshall Plan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe766e3eec85e375820b28b", "question": "You can find Grand Teton National Park in which U.S. state?", "answer": "Wyoming", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59524521736d4be723796b6b", "question": "What French impressionist painter died in 1926", "answer": "Claude Monet", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338950", "question": "What Mozart opera focuses on fiancee swapping as its theme?", "answer": "Cosi fan tutte", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c621", "question": "Which two elements are the most common in the universe?", "answer": "Hydrogen and Helium", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b54d", "question": "What is the complementary colour of red?", "answer": "Green", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a81a", "question": "What Texas city is nicknamed \"The Yellow Rose of Texas\"?", "answer": "Amarillo", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5eb737c95e259d786908732c", "question": "Who was the Bolshevik leader that was exiled by Joseph Stalin after Vladimir Lenin\u2019s death?", "answer": "Leon Trotsky", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe69ef420565ad31a57c789", "question": "Who was the first President to deliver his inaugural address entirely from memory?", "answer": "Franklin Pierce", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aca1", "question": "What is the name of the first nuclear-powered submarine?", "answer": "USS Nautilus", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8b4", "question": "What word meaning \"loss of memory\" comes from the Greek for forgetfulness?", "answer": "Amnesia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adbb", "question": "What was the first US city to have a public school system?", "answer": "Boston", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397c9", "question": "In the 1994 movie \"Jumanji\", a stampede is released, what is the last animal to appear?", "answer": "Rhinoceros", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cef", "question": "What artist performed the song titled \"Doo Wop\"?", "answer": "Lauryn Hill", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339580", "question": "In which sci-fi movie does an alien race live on Earth in slum-like conditions in South Africa?", "answer": "District 9", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1f1", "question": "Who was the only two-term president of the Republic of Texas?", "answer": "Sam Houston", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2a4", "question": "For what movie did Humphrey Bogart win his only Oscar?", "answer": "The African Queen", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c18b", "question": "Vinnie Jones was associated with which sport?", "answer": "Soccer", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5c88e83422f44c2d77a29c46", "question": "Reaching 20,320 feet (6,194 meters) above sea level, Denali is located in what US state?", "answer": " Alaska", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fef5e7b6ce05a3942286e34", "question": "Whose 2018 LP is titled \"Beautiful People Will Ruin Your Life\"?", "answer": "The Wombats", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133acf8", "question": "Which political party was former Prime Minister Tony Blair the leader of?", "answer": "The Labour Party", "category": "history"}, {"id": "592eb163f83302ff91e464a7", "question": "Who directed the 1999 film \"Office Space\"?", "answer": "Mike Judge", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abd3", "question": "Hamilton is the capital of which British Overseas Territory?", "answer": "Bermuda", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bca1", "question": "What Crayola color became \"midnight blue\" in 1958?", "answer": "Prussian blue", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133970b", "question": "What is Woody Allen's birth-name?", "answer": "Allan Stewart Konigsberg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5e72c93ad0874f1a5e2d1c1d", "question": "How many shower curtain rings does the typical shower curtain have?", "answer": "12", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a828", "question": "In which US city is the United States Naval Academy located?", "answer": "Annapolis, Maryland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5e72ccfcd0874f1a5e2d1c26", "question": "What is a \"Winkle Picker\" or \"Winklepicker\"?", "answer": "An English long pointed shoe", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b82a", "question": "How many instruments accompany someone singing \"a cappella\"?", "answer": "None", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bbe", "question": "What popular designer was responsible for the wardrobe of \"Kika and The Cook\"?", "answer": "Jean Paul Gaultier", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c80d", "question": "What kind of bean produces the Asian-style bean sprouts?", "answer": "Mung beans", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe7ccad877e98cb97778a29", "question": "What is the capital city of American Samoa, a group of islands in the South Pacific?", "answer": "Pogo pogo", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133baae", "question": "What company helped the US Army Corps of Engineers develop the \"walkie-talkie\" in the early 1930\u2019s?", "answer": "Motorola", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3c2", "question": "Which of Hitler's deputies flew to Scotland in 1941 to try and negotiate peace with the UK?\u00a0", "answer": "Rudolf Hess", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd2d2ca2596a59cbdfbd393", "question": "What state is also known as the Volunteer State?", "answer": "Tennessee", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe6a9e020565ad31a57c80c", "question": "Whose image is on the U.S. half-dollar from 1916 to 1947?", "answer": "Lady Liberty", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5990f916fa5fdd6dd25324f4", "question": "Dendrochronology is better known as what?", "answer": "Ring dating", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5feddd1c6ce05a3942286da0", "question": "Heisenberg is the nickname of the main character in which popular television series?", "answer": "Breaking Bad", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398e0", "question": "What year saw the release of the movie \"Back to the Future\"?", "answer": "1985", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391f9", "question": "In which 1998 movie did the main character said \"You got the wrong guy. I'm the Dude, man.\"?", "answer": "The Big Lebowski", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ab9c", "question": "The port of Piraeus is located in which country?", "answer": "Greece", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390c4", "question": "Who wrote the 1897 horror novel \"Dracula\"?", "answer": "Bram Stoker", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe69e6620565ad31a57c783", "question": "Benito Mussolini died by what method?", "answer": "He was shot", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e0d", "question": "What author wore a trademark dyed-green carnation in his lapel in 1890s London?", "answer": "Oscar Wilde", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58ec23158dc25ca9e12ef62d", "question": "Who did Jersey Joe Walcott defeat at age 37 to win the heavyweight title?", "answer": "Ezzard Charles", "category": "general"}]